[
    {
        "title" : "Wipeout"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "On July 25th 2000 a Concorde plane crashed into a hotel, causing 113 fatalities. In which country did this event take place?",
      "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Who was President of the USA at the beginning of the new millennium?",
        "answer": "Bill Clinton"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which major art gallery opened in Bankside in London in the year 2000?",
        "answer": "Tate Modern"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "In which city were the Summer Olympic Games held in the year 2000?",
        "answer": "Sydney"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Who became Londonâ€™s first elected mayor in the year 2000?",
        "answer": "Ken Livingstone"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which British doctor was sentenced to life imprisonment on 31st January 2000?",
        "answer": "Harold Shipman"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What was stolen from Bletchley Park Museum in April 2000?",
        "answer": "An Enigma Machine"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which TV reality show aired for the first time in Britain on 14th July 2000?",
        "answer": "Big Brother"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Who became the first ever boxer to be knighted in 2000?",
        "answer": "Henry Cooper"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What is the name of the footbridge across the River Thames which opened in June 2000 but was closed days later because it wobbled?",
        "answer": "The Millennium Bridge"
    }
]
